mentalreporter.com 2018-02-18

# Privacy Policy - MentalReporter.com

Our Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, share and protect information in connection with MentalReporter services (collectively, the “Service”), and your choices about the collection and use of your information. This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”), and other information described in this policy, gathered when you are using or accessing the Services. Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, services and applications, such as Facebook (“Third Party Services”) that you elect to access through the Service or to individuals that we do not manage or employ. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access.

What Information Do We Collect?

The information we gather enables us to personalize, improve and continue to operate the Services. In connection with certain aspects of the Services, we may request, collect, use, share, and/or display some of your Personal Information. We collect the following types of information from our users.

Account Information:

When you create an Account, you will provide information, such as your username, password and email address. You acknowledge that this information may be personal to you, and by creating an Account on the Services and providing Personal Information to us, you allow others, including us, to identify you. If you access the Services through Facebook credentials, we may automatically collect certain information, such as your name, picture, and email address. We will use all information available through Facebook in accordance with Facebook’s policies and your preferences selected through Facebook. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services, when we feel such information is important. You may unsubscribe from these messages at any time.

User Profile Information:

User profile information including your username and other information you enter may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Services. We will not reveal user email addresses to other users of the Site.

Information Collected Automatically:

Generally, the Services automatically collect usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to the Site or mobile application. We may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure. This type of aggregate data enables us and third parties authorized by us to figure out how often individuals use parts of the Services so that we can analyze and improve them.

Email Communications:

We may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us by confirming the subscription service. We use this confirmation to improve our Services, including customer service.

Information Collected Using Cookies:

Cookies are pieces of text that may be provided to your computer through your web browser when you access a website. Your browser stores cookies in a manner associated with each website you visit. We use cookies to enable our servers to recognize your web browser and tell us how and when you visit the Site, share our content, and otherwise use the Services through the Internet. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking  
full advantage of the website. This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer. For example, third party websites to which a link points may set cookies on your computer.

Information You Elect to Share:

You may access other Third Party Services through the Services, for example by clicking on links to those Third Party Services from within the Site. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of these Third Party Services, and you are responsible for reading and understanding those Third Party Services’ privacy policies.  
We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been posted.

Updated : 21/11/2014
